https://asap.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
RESEARCH - EDUCATION - SUPPORT
Search for:
HOMEABOUTBoard of DirectorsProfessional StaffMedical Advisory BoardFOR PATIENTSFOR PATIENTSComprehensive Guide for PatientsPatient HandbookQ & A for Newly DiagnosedASAP Fact SheetGlossaryCONDITIONSChiari MalformationSyringomyeliaChiari & Syringomyelia 101Medical ArticlesRelated DisordersCanine SyringomyeliaSUPPORTLocal Support GroupsOnline Support GroupsTelephone SupportPersonal StoriesCONFERENCESVirtual Conference 2020ASAP’s L.E.A.R.N! Points ProgramVIDEOSRESOURCESBecome a MemberParents ResourcesFor KidsInternationalScholarshipsASAP ConnectionsNewsRESEARCHFellowships and AwardsWAYS TO HELPWays to HelpVolunteer NowTogether We Can Walk & RollDonate to ASAPVisit our Awareness StoreCONTACTDONATE
Search for:
HOMEABOUTBoard of DirectorsProfessional StaffMedical Advisory BoardFOR PATIENTSFOR PATIENTSComprehensive Guide for PatientsPatient HandbookQ & A for Newly DiagnosedASAP Fact SheetGlossaryCONDITIONSChiari MalformationSyringomyeliaChiari & Syringomyelia 101Medical ArticlesRelated DisordersCanine SyringomyeliaSUPPORTLocal Support GroupsOnline Support GroupsTelephone SupportPersonal StoriesCONFERENCESVirtual Conference 2020ASAP’s L.E.A.R.N! Points ProgramVIDEOSRESOURCESBecome a MemberParents ResourcesFor KidsInternationalScholarshipsASAP ConnectionsNewsRESEARCHFellowships and AwardsWAYS TO HELPWays to HelpVolunteer NowTogether We Can Walk & RollDonate to ASAPVisit our Awareness StoreCONTACTDONATE
Search for:
HOMEABOUTBoard of DirectorsProfessional StaffMedical Advisory BoardFOR PATIENTSFOR PATIENTSComprehensive Guide for PatientsPatient HandbookQ & A for Newly DiagnosedASAP Fact SheetGlossaryCONDITIONSChiari MalformationSyringomyeliaChiari & Syringomyelia 101Medical ArticlesRelated DisordersCanine SyringomyeliaSUPPORTLocal Support GroupsOnline Support GroupsTelephone SupportPersonal StoriesCONFERENCESVirtual Conference 2020ASAP’s L.E.A.R.N! Points ProgramVIDEOSRESOURCESBecome a MemberParents ResourcesFor KidsInternationalScholarshipsASAP ConnectionsNewsRESEARCHFellowships and AwardsWAYS TO HELPWays to HelpVolunteer NowTogether We Can Walk & RollDonate to ASAPVisit our Awareness StoreCONTACTDONATE
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policydpb2012-10-30T14:56:00-05:00
American Syringomyelia & Chiari Alliance Project, Inc. respects your privacy and we want you to be confident in sharing your information with us. We’ve written the following statement to disclose any of the information we gather while you are using our site.
We do not share any identifiable information with any third party at any point in your relationship with us without your permission.
We collect certain technical information to insure that our site is working properly. For example, when you are browsing, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to help administer our Web site.
American Syringomyelia & Chiari Alliance Project, Inc. does not use cookies to retrieve any information about you from your computer.
The information we may request from you is outlined below. If you have any further questions, please feel free to contact us at info@ASAP.org
Email Address: If you wish to be contacted by email, we require that you provide us with your email address.
Contact Info: When a user decides to become a member of ASAP.ORG, we collect complete contact information, i.e. full name, address and phone number as well as other personal informations. This information is only used by American Syringomyelia Alliance Project, Inc. to validate the user’s identity and to provide the services by American Syringomyelia & Chiari Alliance Project, Inc..
We take reasonable precautions to maintain the security of the personal information you provide to our site. Additionally, third parties displaying advertisements on our site may use cookies. American Syringomyelia & Chiari Alliance Project, Inc. does not control the use of cookies by third parties. The use of cookies by these companies is subject to their own privacy policies, which you may review by visiting their websites.
Our site contains links to other Web sites. American Syringomyelia & Chiari Alliance Project, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at info@ASAP.org
Direct Mail and Email Communications
ASAP may collect personal information such as names, mailing addresses, titles, fax numbers and email addresses from donors, volunteers or others who request information from our organization.
ASAP does not rent, sell or share your personal information with any other organizations. We take reasonable precautions to protect your information including the use of a password protected database.
ASAP does use names and addresses collected to communicate to donors through our direct mail program, email updates and newsletters.
If at any time you do not wish to receive email or direct mail communication or solicitations regarding services, programs, or fundraising or if you need to update or change your contact information, email us at info@ASAP.org or mail your request to:
ASAP
PO Box 1586
Longview, TX 75606
Go to Top
